<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bootstrap on AquaAccoustics</title><link>https://duriya-rehan.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-whale.college/tags/bootstrap/</link><description>Recent content in Bootstrap on AquaAccoustics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>Duriya Rehan</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:00:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://duriya-rehan.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-whale.college/tags/bootstrap/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bootstrap 5.3.0</title><link>https://duriya-rehan.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-whale.college/post/bootstrap-5-3-0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://duriya-rehan.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-whale.college/post/bootstrap-5-3-0/</guid><description>{ .img-fluid }
It’s official, the final stable release of v5.3.0 has landed! It’s been a monumental effort to revamp our codebase for CSS variables and color modes, one that will see continued changes leading up to an eventual Bootstrap 6. And we’re so excited to finally ship it!
On top of all the work that’s gone into this release, a lot has happened behind the scenes since we shipped our pre-releases.</description></item><item><title>AquaAccoustics alpha</title><link>https://duriya-rehan.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-whale.college/post/hugo-bootstrap-theme/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 13:35:02 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://duriya-rehan.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-whale.college/post/hugo-bootstrap-theme/</guid><description>Analyze whale songs effectively using this site!
Open-source MIT Licensed Hugo Theme, using Bootstrap 5.
🛡️ Real-time Song Analysis
Instantly decode the secrets of the deep with real-time analysis of whale songs, uncovering species details, emotional states, and hidden messages.
⚡ Species Identification
Dive into the diversity of the ocean with precise whale species identification from their unique songs, complete with visual and auditory guides.
📈 Mood Interpretation
Explore the emotional spectrum of whales through song, with intuitive mood interpretations visualized by color codes and emoticons.</description></item><item><title>Bootstrap 5.2.0 beta</title><link>https://duriya-rehan.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-whale.college/post/bootstrap-5-2-0-beta/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 13:00:44 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://duriya-rehan.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-whale.college/post/bootstrap-5-2-0-beta/</guid><description>{ .img-fluid }
It’s the biggest release since v5 itself—Bootstrap v5.2.0-beta1 is here! This release features redesigned docs, CSS variables for all our components, responsive offcanvas, new helpers and utilities, refined buttons and inputs, and lots of improvements under the hood.
Given the size of the update and time since our last release, we’re doing something different and shipping it as a beta first. Keep reading for details.</description></item></channel></rss>